当我还是个实习生 或者第一年受训的医生
When I was an intern, or a first-year doctor in training,
我就知道我的状态出了问题
I knew something was wrong with me.
我时常失眠 郁郁寡欢
I had trouble sleeping, I had difficulty feeling joy,
我会在不合适的时候有哭泣的冲动
I was prone to crying at inopportune times.
更糟糕的是 我难以和病人沟通
Even worse, I had trouble connecting with patients.
我觉得我不能让任何人感到高兴
I felt like I couldn't please anyone,
我发现我and I found myself susceptible to feelings of despair and panic.
I'm a physician! And if I do say so myself, a very well trained one.
Yet it took an intern support group, the social worker that ran it,
close friends and my then fiancee and now wife
to convince me that I might need help.
Even if I couldn't acknowledge it,
they could see I was suffering from depression.
I wasn't alone! that's the topic of this week's healthcare triage.
Last month the study in JAMA
reviewed all the literature on depression and depressive symptoms in resident physicians.
They found more than 50 studies on the subject.
Researches show that almost 30% of resident physician
suffer from either symptoms, or a diagnosis of depression.
The numbers and how they compare to other professions are almost beside the point.
Physicians are in a unique position of needing to care for others continuously,
that strain coupled with an inability to help themselves,
leaves both patients and doctors at risk.
Longitudinal studies or those that follow resident over the course of their training,
found that the rate of depressive issues in residents
increased more than 15 percent within a year of beginning training.
Worse, physicians exist in a profession where admitting a problem
carries with it a stigma that's more impactful than in some others.
A study published in 2008 surveyed physicians in Michigan,
asking them about their work experiences as well as their depressive symptoms.
More than 11 percent reported moderate to severe depression scores.
About a quarter of them reported knowing a doctor
whose professional standing had been hurt by being depressed.
Physicians with moderate to severe depression
had a decrease in work productivity and job satisfaction.
They were also two to three times more likely to say
that they were worried about or had difficulty getting mental health care
while the Americans with Disabilities Act passed in 1990
prohibits employers from asking broad questions about illnesses when people apply for jobs,
state medical licensing board still ask specific questions about mental health.
Because of this, physicians are much more likely to avoid treatment
but also more likely to self medicate.
Sometimes that medication is potentially appropriate, as with anti-depressants.
Often it is not.
A 2012 study in JAMA surgery found that
more than 15% of the members of the American College of Surgeons
had a score on screening test consistent with alcohol abuse or dependence.
Among female surgeons the prevalence was more than 25%.
Those who were depressed were significantly more likely to abuse or be dependent on alcohol.
doctors have much easier access to drugs than others as well.
Because of this they are more likely to misuse prescription drugs than the general population.
Anesthesiologist have access to even more drugs than other physicians
and their problems are even more common.
A 2005 study of anesthesia residency training programs,
found that eighty percent of them reported experiences with impaired residents
and almost 20% had experiences with at least one abuse-related death of a doctrine training.
Unfortunately, depression and substance abuse can lead to further problems including suicide
more than 6 percent of surgeons report suicidal ideation in the last year
yet only one-quarter of then sought any kind of mental health treatment.
Most who did not fear the doing so would affect their ability to obtain a license,
even though they were worried about killing themselves.
The problem is even worse among medical trainees.
About 6 percent of them reported thinking about suicide in the last two weeks.
Those with a history of depression
were almost four times as likely to report recent suicidal thoughts as those without.
Too many doctors act on suicidal impulses as well.
It's estimated that about 400 physicians commit suicide each year,
that's about three times as many doctors
as were in my medical school class at the University of Pennsylvania.
Meta-analyses estimate the rate of suicide among male physicians
is a hundred and forty percent that of the general population.
Among female physicians it's almost two hundred and thirty percent.
What makes this important to discuss
is not theprevalence of depression in physicians and trainees,
although it's clearly too high,
it's not whether physicians have the highest suicide rate of any professional,
although many people argue that they do.
The critical issue here is that too many physicians especially trainees
suffer in silence, afraid to ask for help
for fear that they will be punished professionally if not personally.
I've always been very open about my time in residency,
and how depression someone robbed me of a few years of my life.
When I look back, I think the constant pressure to help others
coupled with frequent feelings of helplessness wait on me,
a lack of sleep and being away from family and friends left me vulnerable.
Seeing children I've bonded with and cared for deeply suffer and die
was often more than I could bear.
And I think some part of me whether it be physical or behavioral
is also predisposed to anxiety and depression.
But I'm lucky, thanks to the support of those who love me
as well as two excellent therapist, I'm no longer depressed.
I remain vigilant, however, against a recurrence.
It's important for me and for all physicians to stay on top of their mental health
and not wait for a crisis to act.
I've also felt fortunate to be in a specialty: pediatrics and a focus: research
where I didn't fear being found out.
Many colleagues still recoil when I talked openly about therapy,
or how I plan to go for the rest of my life.
I'm sure they'll find this episode concerning as well.
But we can't not talk about this.
Too many of us are suffering and if they can't get help from others,
they may try and fail to help themselves.
Suicide is always a tragedy. A physician committing suicide is a travesty.