when I was an intern or a first-year
doctor in training I knew something was
wrong with me I had trouble sleeping I
had difficulty feeling joy I was prone
to crying at inopportune times even
worse I had trouble connecting with
patients I felt like I couldn't please
anyone and I found myself susceptible to
feelings of despair and panic I'm a
physician!  and if I do say so myself a very
well trained one yet it took an intern
support group the social worker that ran
it close friends and my then fiancee and
now wife to convince me that I might
need help even if I couldn't acknowledge
it they could see I was suffering from
depression I wasn't alone that's the
topic of this week's healthcare triage
last month the study in JAMA reviewed all
the literature on depression and
depressive symptoms and resident
physicians they found more than 50
studies on the subject research shows
that almost 30% of resident physician
suffer from either symptoms or a
diagnosis of depression the numbers and
how they compare to other professions
are almost beside the point
physicians are in a unique position of
needing to care for others continuously
that strain coupled with an inability
to help themselves
leaves both patients and doctors at risk
longitudinal studies or those that
follow resident over the course of their
training found that the rate of
depressive issues in residents
increased more than 15 percent within a
follow resident over the course of their
training found that the rate of
depressive issues in residents
increased more than 15 percent within a
year of beginning training. worse, physicians
exist in a profession where admitting a
problem carries with it a stigma that's
more impactful than in some others
a study published in 2008 surveyed
physicians in Michigan asking them about
their work experiences as well as their
depressive symptoms more than 11 percent
reported moderate to severe depression
scores about a quarter of them reported
knowing a doctor whose professional
standing had been hurt by being
depressed positions with moderate to
severe depression had a decrease in work
productivity and job satisfaction they
were also two to three times more likely
to say that they were worried about or
had difficulty getting mental health
care while the Americans with
Disabilities Act passed in 1990 prohibits
employers from asking broad questions
about illnesses when people apply for
jobs
state medical licensing board still ask
specific questions about mental health
because of this physicians are much more
likely to avoid treatment but also more
likely to self medicate sometimes that
medication is potentially appropriate as
with anti-depressants often it is not a
2012 study in JAMA surgery found that
more than 15% of the members of the
American College of Surgeons had a
scoreless screening tests consistent
with alcohol abuse or dependence among
female surgeons the prevalence was more
than 25% those who were depressed were
significantly more likely to abuse or be
dependent on alcohol
doctors have much easier access to drugs
than others as well because of this they
are more likely to misuse prescription
drugs than the general population
anesthesiologist have access to even
more drugs than other physicians and
their problems are even more common 2005
study of anesthesia residency training
programs found the eighty percent of
them reported experiences with impaired
residence and almost 20% had experiences
with at least one abuse related death of
a doctrine training unfortunately
depression and substance abuse can lead
residence and almost 20% had experiences
with at least one abuse related death of
a doctrine training unfortunately
depression and substance abuse can lead
to further problems including suicide
more than 6 percent of surgeons report
suicidal ideation in the last year you don't
**______** one-quarter of then **__saw?__* any kind of mental
health treatment most who did not fear
the doing so would affect their ability
to obtain a license even though they
were worried about killing themselves
the problem is even worse among medical
trainees about 6 percent of them
reported thinking about suicide in the
last two weeks those with a history of
depression were almost four times as
likely to report recent suicidal
thoughts as those without too many
doctors act on suicidal impulses as well
depression were almost four times as
likely to report recent suicidal
thoughts as those without too many
doctors act on suicidal impulses as well
it's estimated that about 400 physicians
commit suicide each year that's about
three times as many doctors is wearing
my medical school class at the
University of Pennsylvania meta-analyses
estimate the rate of suicide among male
physicians is a hundred and forty
percent that of the general population
among female physicians it's almost two
hundred and thirty percent what makes
this important to discuss is not the
prevalence of depression and positions
and trainees although it's clearly too
high it's not whether physicians have
the highest suicide rate of any
professional though many people argue
that they do the critical issue here is
that too many positions especially
trainees suffer in silence afraid to ask
for help prepare that they will be
punished professionally if not
personally I've always been very open
about my time in residency
depression someone robbed me of a few
years of my life when I look back I
think the constant pressure to help
others coupled with frequent feelings of
helplessness wait on me a lack of sleep
and being away from family and friends
let me vulnerable seeing children have
bonded with and cared for deeply suffer
helplessness wait on me a lack of sleep
and being away from family and friends
let me vulnerable seeing children have
bonded with and cared for deeply suffer
and die was often more than I could bear
and I think some part of me whether it
be physical behavior all is also
predisposed anxiety and depression but
I'm lucky thanks to the support of those
who love me as well as two excellent
therapist I'm no longer depressed I
remain vigilant however against a
recurrence it's important for me and for
all positions to stay on top of their
mental health not weight for a crisis to
act of also felt fortunate to be in a
specialty pediatrics and a focus
research where I didn't fear being found
out many colleagues still require when I
talked openly about their or how I plan
specialty pediatrics and a focus
research where I didn't fear being found
out many colleagues still require when I
talked openly about their or how I plan
to go for the rest of my life I'm sure
they'll find this episode concerning as
well but we can't not talk about this
too many of us are suffering and if they
can't get help from others they may try
and fail to help themselves
suicide is always a tragedy a physician
committing suicide is a travesty
healthcare triage supported in part by
viewers like you to pay tree on a
service that allows you to support the
show through a monthly donation your
support makes this show bigger and
better especially like to thank our
service that allows you to support the
show through a monthly donation your
support makes this show bigger and
better especially like to thank our
research associate joe savitz give a
special shout out to Jonathan done and
thank our surgeon admiral sam thanks Joe
and John Danks am more information can
be found at bay tree on dot com slash
health care tria
下载YouTube(cc)字幕请访问http://zhuwei.me/youtube